affiliatebot.com 2006-12-23

# AffiliateBot.com - Privacy Policy

Welcome to the AffiliateBot.com's Privacy Policy page. AffiliateBot.com have created this Privacy Policy for the protection of AffiliateBot.com's Members ("Merchants and Affiliates"). Please read this privacy policy carefully since by visiting this Web Site (the 'Site') and sharing information in this Site you agree to be bound by the terms and conditions of this Privacy Policy. 

**RESPONSIBLE ONLINE MARKETING**

AffiliateBot.com believes that protecting the privacy of the Site users is essential in order to give them the best user experience AffiliateBot.com can possibly deliver to ensure that their experience with the Site is a positive one. With this in mind, AffiliateBot.com proceeds to create significant results for Merchants and Affiliates in the AffiliateBot.com's affiliate program network in professional and ethical ways without compromising the privacy of the Site users. 

Consumer Privacy l Client Privacy 

**CONSUMER PRIVACY**

**I. INFORMATION COLLECTED FROM THE SITE USERS**

**A. Personally Identifiable Information (hereafter referred as "PII").**   
The AffiliateBot.com Site is designed to promote and facilitate the AffiliateBot.com affiliate marketing programs with merchants and affiliates. AffiliateBot.com does not collect any PII from individual Internet consumers unless they contact AffiliateBot.com on his/her own initiative or respond to an AffiliateBot.com advertisement and provide any PII. AffiliateBot.com will not request or collect sensitive PII such as an Internet user's medical/health conditions; racial or ethnic origin; political, religious or philosophical beliefs or affiliations; trade union membership or sex life. 

**B. Non-Personally Identifiable Information (hereafter referred as "Non-PII").**   
The AffiliateBot.com Site uses cookies to keep track of member activities, purchases and other online transactions on this Site and to enhance user experience for online transactions. Cookies are small data files commonly used on the Internet to help optimize and personalize the Internet end user experience and identify repeat visitors to Web sites. These cookies are activated when a user responds to or views an Internet advertisement served by the Site. These cookies provide the Site with information for the purpose of paying third-parties commissions when certain actions are generated on the Advertiser's Web Site. Non-PII does not enable AffiliateBot.com to personally identify an Internet user. AffiliateBot.com reserves the right to retain all ad delivery and reporting data as long as reasonably necessary for accounting and audit purposes. 

**II. SHARING OF INFORMATION**

AffiliateBot.com may make any PII provided in responding to an advertisement available to the company sponsoring the advertisement, as well as to other trusted third parties in accordance with the terms of this privacy policy. As a result, you may receive information on additional products, services or offers that may be of interest to you, based on the PII provided by you.   

AffiliateBot.com may share PII (including information that has been enhanced with information from other sources) with advertisers, third party marketers, our affiliated entities for their online and/or offline marketing programs. While AffiliateBot.com strongly encourages clients and partners to adopt responsible approaches to Internet marketing, AffiliateBot.com is not responsible for the information practices of clients or their partners. The collection, use, and disclosure of any information by clients and partners are subject to their respective privacy policies, which may differ from AffiliateBot.com's privacy policy.   

AffiliateBot.com may release accounts and any other personal information should we think that the release is appropriate in order to respond to a subpoena or otherwise comply with the law; enforce or apply our Terms and Conditions and other agreements; or protect the rights, property, or safety of AffiliateBot.com or others. This includes exchanging information with other companies and organizations for fraud protection. 

**III. SECURITY**

AffiliateBot.com employs professional industry standard security measures to ensure the security of all data. Any data that is stored on the Site's servers will be treated as proprietary and confidential material and will not be available to the public. AffiliatrBot.com has an internal security policy with respect to the confidentiality of customer and other data, allowing access only to those employees or third parties who have a need to access such information for the purpose of delivering AffiliateBot.com products and services effectively by means of user login and password requirements. AffiliateBot.com routinely evaluates its data security practices in order to identify security threats or opportunities for improvement. 

Transmission of data over the Internet is not guaranteed to be completely secure. It is possible for third parties not under AffiliateBot.com's control to intercept or access transmissions or private communications unlawfully. While we take advanced security measures to protect your PII, AffiliateBot.com cannot ensure or warrant the security of any information you transmit through the Site. You acknowledge and assume this risk when communicating with or through this Site. 

**IV. CONSENT AND CHANGES**

AffiliateBot.com reserves the exclusive right to modify or update this Privacy Policy from time to time should it be necessary or for legal purposes. Any changes on this page would be published in the Site and AffiliateBot.com will update the effective date so that you are always aware of the information we collect, how we use it, and under what circumstances we disclose it. Except as otherwise required by law, modifications to this Privacy Policy will not affect the privacy of data collected by AffiliateBot.com prior to the effective date of the policy change. 

**V. CHILDREN'S PRIVACY**

AffiliateBot.com is very sensitive on the issue of children's privacy and strives to protect the privacy of children using the Internet. The Site, products, and services are not developed for or directed at children. Children (persons under the age of 18) are not eligible to do business with us. We do not collect personal information from any person we actually know is under the age of 13\. Should we come to know of a certain user who has registered with us is under the minimum required age, we will remove the user immediately. 

**VI. SPAM POLICY**

AffiliateBot.com is committed to professional and ethical Internet practices and prohibits any Â“e-mail spamÂ” of any kind by AffiliateBot.com or our partners, merchants, affiliates and any other entities or individuals associated with us. We however, cannot fully guarantee a Â“spam freeÂ” experience to our users as we do not control the activities of our partners, merchants, affiliates and any other entities or individuals associated with us. 

Please note that an advertiser is required to provide an opt-out mechanism for consumers to unsubscribe from future emails about the advertiser. Should you experience any "e-mail spam" as a result of using this Site, look for the opt-out mechanism to unsubscribe yourself and if necessary, contact us here. 

**CONTACT US**

If you have questions or concerns regarding the AffiliateBot.com Privacy Policy, please contact us here. 

**MERCHANTS AND AFFILIATES PRIVACY**

**I. INFORMATION WE COLLECT FROM MERCHANTS AND AFFILIATES**

**A. Personally Identifiable Information (hereafter referred as "PII").**   
AffiliateBot.com collects PII from all Merchants and Affiliates who wishes to work with AffiliateBot.com as the collection of this information is a part of our normal business practices. Merchants will be asked to provide personally identifiable data during the sign up and registration process. Examples of personally identifiable data that may be requested include name, address, phone number, email address, and social security number, tax ID number, etc. AffiliateBot.com will not request or collect from our Merchants and Affiliates sensitive PII such as medical/health conditions; racial or ethnic origin; political, religious or philosophical beliefs or affiliations; trade union membership or sex life. 

**B. Non-Personally Identifiable Information (hereafter referred as "Non-PII").**  
AffiliateBot.com may use cookies and log files to optimize and personalize the Merchants' and Affiliates' experience and allow AffiliateBot.com to monitor site traffic patterns. 

**II. SHARING OF INFORMATION**

AffiliateBot.com does not use any personally identifiable data about our Merchants and Affiliates for profiling purposes. All PII collected from Merchants and Affiliates is intended for administrative use (e.g., accounting, pay-out and performance reporting), for which purpose such data are required. 

AffiliateBot.com may provide email address or basic account data or both to our Merchants and Affiliates to facilitate a potential or continued business relationship between the Merchants and Affiliates. While we strongly encourage our Merchants and Affiliates to adopt responsible approaches to online marketing, we are not responsible for the information practices of our Merchants and Affiliates or their partners. The collection, use, and disclosure of information by Merchants and Affiliates and/or their partners are subject to their respective privacy policies, which may differ from our policy. 

AffiliateBot.com may from time to time use Merchants' and Affiliates' PII in order to communicate with our network of hosts via email newsletters or other avenues in order to offer strategic marketing information or other communications to assist in business related activities. In the event that a Merchant or an Affiliate wishes not to have their PII used for these purposes, they may elect to opt-out from future communications. 

AffiliateBot.com may release accounts and any other personal information should we think that the release is appropriate in order to respond to a subpoena or otherwise comply with the law; enforce or apply our Terms and Conditions and other agreements; or protect the rights, property, or safety of AffiliateBot.com or others. This includes exchanging information with other companies and organizations for fraud protection. 

**III. SECURITY**

AffiliateBot.com employs professional industry standard security measures to ensure the security of all data. Any data that is stored on the Site's servers will be treated as proprietary and confidential material and will not be available to the public. AffiliatrBot.com has an internal security policy with respect to the confidentiality of customer and other data, allowing access only to those employees or third parties who have a need to access such information for the purpose of delivering AffiliateBot.com products and services effectively by means of user login and password requirements. AffiliateBot.com routinely evaluates its data security practices in order to identify security threats or opportunities for improvement. 

Transmission of data over the Internet is not guaranteed to be completely secure. It is possible for third parties not under AffiliateBot.com's control to intercept or access transmissions or private communications unlawfully. While we take advanced security measures to protect your PII, AffiliateBot.com cannot ensure or warrant the security of any information you transmit through the Site. You acknowledge and assume this risk when communicating with or through this Site. 

**IV. CONSENT AND CHANGES**

AffiliateBot.com reserves the exclusive right to modify or update this Privacy Policy from time to time should it be necessary or for legal purposes. Any changes on this page would be published in the Site and AffiliateBot.com will update the effective date so that you are always aware of the information we collect, how we use it, and under what circumstances we disclose it. Except as otherwise required by law, modifications to this Privacy Policy will not affect the privacy of data collected by AffiliateBot.com prior to the effective date of the policy change. 

**V. CONTACT US**

If you have questions or concerns regarding the AffiliateBot.com Privacy Policy, please contact us here. 

Published April 26th, 2006 Copyright Â© 2006, AffiliateBot.com All rights reserved. 

**I HAVE READ THIS AGREEMENT AND AGREE TO ALL OF THE LISTED PROVISIONS CONTAINED HEREIN.**
